翻译: 南希 元气 马西萝卜
各位 早上好
Morning, everyone.
早上好 警监
Morning, sir.
校对: FENGYUDEER
看哪
Hey, look.
咱俩衣服都洒上吃的了
We're food stain buds.
你那是什么吃的 粥吗
Who are you wearing? Porridge?
后期: 尘世劫
这个是
Um,
燕麦
oatmeal.
嗯
Hmm.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
压制: 怪查理
他都不擦掉的
He didn't even wipe it off.
他已经放弃人生了吧
He's totally given up on life.
这是孤单
It's loneliness.
自从Kevin离开他去了巴黎休假
Ever since Kevin left for his sabbatical in Paris,
他跟变了个人似的
he hasn't been the same.
我想让他多出去参加些活动
I tried to get him out of the house.
我邀请他去参加酒吧问答 但他拒绝了我
I invited him to bar trivia, but he turned me down,
不是说我们"牛顿谜语队"需要他做外援
not that Trivia Newton John needed the help.
我们是全国排名靠前的队伍 没啥大不了的
We're nationally ranked. It's no big deal.
是没什么大不了的
You're right, it's not.
你们都只是些好心的小傻瓜们
Well, aren't you all just a bunch of big-hearted dum-dums.
你们想让他不那么寂寞
You want to make him feel less lonely?
你们应该这么做
This is how you do it.
- 一袋卷宗  - 对 他是工作狂
- A case file? - Yeah, dude loves work.
我以为你的案子都结了
I thought all your cases were closed.
你昨晚一直在炫耀这事
You were bragging about it so much last night,
邻居吵架我都没听到结局
I couldn't hear the end of the neighbors' fight.
结局就是俩人做爱了 他们总是那样
It ended in sex. It always does.
不过我完全没性趣
It didn't make me horny.
这是我第一年当警探的一个旧案子
It's a cold case from my first year as a detective.
罪犯又有新活动了
Is it active again?
没 但Holt不需要知道这点
No, but Holt doesn't have to know that.
所以你打算撒谎
So you're gonna lie to him?
不 我要用一种方法 让他忘却悲伤
No, I'm going to make him forget about his sadness through the power of...
那就是 分散注意力
distraction!
我消失啦
He's gone.
神烦警探
第三季 第十二集
电波诚译
警监 早上好
Ah, hola, mi capitan.
你可能会问 为什么我要说意大利语
Why am I speaking Italian, you might ask?
那是西班牙语
That was Spanish.
好吧 语言种类千千万嘛
Yeah, there are too many languages.
我的一个旧案子有新进展了
An old case of mine is starting to heat up,
我需要您老来帮助我 先生
and I'd like your old help to help me solve it, senor?
- 还是西班牙语  - 好吧
- Still Spanish. - Right.
Joey Garibaldi曾经是个黑帮头目
Joey Garibaldi was a mafia lieutenant.
差不多八年前 我已经快抓到他了
About eight years ago, I was closing in on him
但他却销声匿迹了
when he disappeared.
可现在我又听到风声
But now I'm hearing chatter on the street
说他又冒头了
that he's back in town.
你能帮我吗
Will you help me?
嗯 听上去挺有趣 算我一个
Hmm, sounds interesting. Count me in.
太好了 谢谢
Yes! Thank you very much, sir.
再见咯
Uh, good-a bye-a.
绝对是意大利语
Italian.
标准化测试吗
Ooh, standardized tests?
我有个小诀窍
I have a great trick.
拿涂改液涂满所有格子
Fill in all the bubbles with Wite-Out,
再对读卡器动点手脚 大家都能过
jams the machine, everyone passes.
这是我的警督考试的练习题
These are practice for the lieutenant's exam.
真的太难了
They're kicking my butt.
我一直考不到70分
I can't get better than 70%.
C减 这是最完美的分数了
C-minus, the perfect grade--
证明你有点头脑 但还是性感的
you pass, but you're still hot.
Holt警监给了我他的卷子来帮我
Captain Holt gave me his test to help me study.
你瞧瞧阅卷人给他写的评语
Look at what the grader wrote on his essay.
"感谢你写了这篇文章
"Thank you for writing this.
它帮助我成为更好的人"
Reading it made me a better man."
我永远不会成为和Holt一样优秀的领导的
I'll never be as good a leader as Holt.
你不要老想着考试了
You need to stop focusing on tests.
生活中不只有分数和书本
There's more to life than scores and book learning, okay?
看看我 我从没上过专业舞蹈课
Look at me, I've had no official dance training.
但我现在
Yet here I stand...
简直就是舞动的奇迹
a miracle of movement.
你们看见Boyle了吗
Hey, you guys seen Boyle?
他在他桌子底下呢 缩成球了
Yep, he's in a little ball under his desk.
不是吧
Oh, no.
NBC悬疑剧
你昨晚又看<格林>了
Did you watch "Grimm" Again last night?
你明知道看了会做噩梦的
You know it gives you nightmares.
我好伤心
I'm sad.
Jason今早去世了
Jason died this morning.
我很抱歉 太惨了
I'm sorry. That's terrible.
他是你的朋友吗
Is he a friend of yours?
他是我的狗狗
He was my dog.
哦 那就不是什么大事
Oh, okay, so no big deal then.
对我来说是大事
No, it is to me.
不过不用担心
But don't worry,
我会想办法挺过去的
I'll find a way to power through.
哦 天哪
Oh, God.
Jason就是以这个视角看世界的
This is how Jason saw the world.
等一下 Jason就是那条什么都操的狗
Wait, was this your dog that humped everything?
对 他就是这么死的
Yeah, that's how he died.
他本想上我的一双雪地靴
He was going to town on one of my snow boots,
然后他的小心脏没承受住
and his little heart just gave out.
- 他都还没射呢  - 真恶心
- He didn't even finish. - Gross.
总之 我们要去四街的那家运动用品商店去跟线索
Anyway, we have to work a stream of B&E's on 4th Street.
你也该向前看了
It's time for you to move on.
Jackson会是这么希望的
It's what Jackson would've wanted.
- 他叫Jason  - 无所谓 小伙计
- Jason! - Whatever, little buddy.
99分局
下午1:32
警监 谢谢你来见我
Captain, thank you for meeting me.
让你周六加班了 真是不好意思
Sorry to make you work on a Saturday.
别这么说 反正我很闲
No, nonsense, I was free.
Kevin还在巴黎
Kevin is still in Paris.
是吗
Is he?
我都不记得了呢
Wow, I totally forgot about that.
总之 这就是Garibaldi销声匿迹后
Any-hoops, this is all the stuff that we got
我们在他公寓找到的全部东西了
from Garibaldi's apartment after he disappeared.
告诉我你有什么发现
Tell me what you see.
这个人在每张照片里都出现过
This man is in every photograph.
Nick DiTullio
Nick DiTullio.
我八年前就带他去问过话
I actually brought him in eight years ago,
但他什么都不肯说
but he refused to talk.
你知道的 俗话说的好
Of course, you know the saying,
"时间会让每个男人开口的
"Time shall open up the mouth of every man
特别是关于他邻居的真相"
to the truth of his neighbor."
真有这么个俗语的 就别计较这个了
All right, it's a real saying. Let's not dwell on it.
重点是 他肯定会告诉我们Garibaldi的下落
The point is, he's definitely gonna tell us
我不知道Garibaldi在哪
I don't know where Garibaldi is, all right?
我们走得并不近
It's not like we were close.
我只是他的健身教练而已
I was just his trainer at the gym.
那你们为什么经常一起去吃饭
Then why were you always going out to dinner with him?
- 吃意大利面也算健身吗  - 问得好
- Was he doing reps of linguine? - Noice.
拒绝Garibaldi是不可能的 明白吗
Look, you don't say no to Garibaldi, all right?
所以我只让他练胸肌和腹肌
That's why I always let him work his chest and his abs
从不练腿部
and never his legs.
我懂 关键在于平衡
Yeah, the key is balance.
所以我从来不练肌肉
That's why I never work any of it.
如果你们不是来逮捕我的话 我得先走了
Unless you guys are gonna arrest me, I got to go.
健身房那边出了些紧急情况
There's an emergency at the gym.
两个警察来问话 健身房正好出现紧急情况
Emergency at the gym just when two cops show up at his door.
看上去很可疑 我们应该跟踪他
That seems suspicious. We should follow him.
是啊 这案子还真出现了线索
Yeah, this case might actually lead somewhere.
你为什么这么惊讶
Why are you so surprised?
因为这份工作每天都充满惊奇
Because every day on this job is a wonder.
不能更同意了
Damn right it is.
医学检测员 我们中奖了
Medical examiner, jackpot.
那健身房里肯定全是尸体
The gym is full of bodies.
- 这是卫生部  - 哦 天哪
- No, Department of Health. - Oh.
最近很流行腮腺炎
There's been an outbreak of the mumps.
腮腺炎 这词太搞笑了
Mumps, that's a funny word.
这其实是一个很容易传染的重病
It's actually a very serious and highly contagious infectious disease.
但我们不会被传染的
Yeah, but we're fine.
我们也就和那人接触了几秒钟
We were only in contact with that guy for a couple of seconds.
而且 他也没舔我们眼球
Plus, he didn't even lick any of our eyeballs.
你们恐怕都得了腮腺炎
I'm afraid you both have the mumps.
腮腺炎 听起来还是很搞笑
Mumps, still a funny word.
我们不会死吧
Are we gonna die?
所以 你们都得了腮腺炎
So you both have the mumps.
我很抱歉 这病传染性很强
Sorry to say, it's very contagious.
警探 你可能不想呆在这里
You may not want to be here, detective.
哦 没关系的
Oh, it's cool.
我定期打疫苗
I keep up to date on all my vaccinations.
我对很多你们听都没听过的病免疫呢
I'm immune to stuff you've never even heard of.
除了爱吹牛的病
But not immune to braggadocio.
总之 接下来的几个小时内
Anyhow, over the next several hours,
你们很可能会有发烧 疼痛 疲劳的症状
you will more than likely develop fever, aching, fatigue.
这不算什么
Doesn't sound too bad.
还有 酸性食物会带来严重的下颚疼痛
Also, tart foods will cause intense jaw pain,
所以你们最好别吃酸的糖果
so you may want to avoid sour candies.
什么
What?
否则脖子上可能会长甲状腺肿块 很疼
You may get painful goiter-like swelling in your neck
另外 还可能发生睾丸部位的不适
and often extreme testicular discomfort.
- 好吧  - 懂了
- Okay, okay. - Cool, cool.
懂 懂 懂
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
毫无疑问
No doubt.
因为这病毒有极高的传染性
Due the highly contagious nature of the virus,
接下来九天 你们两位将会在家进行隔离
you will both be quarantined to your houses for the next nine days.
哦 孤独的九天
Oh, nine days in isolation.
警监 我很乐意去陪你
Sir, I'd be happy to keep you company.
<Nicholas Nickleby>是英国作家狄更斯所写的小说，被多次改编成影视剧作。
我们可以看PBS电视台播的Nicholas Nickleby传记十部曲
We can watch the ten-part Nicholas Nickleby special on PBS.
我听说电影节奏又慢 时间又长
Hear there's a lot of long, quiet stretches.
我确实喜欢慢节奏时间长的电影
I do love long, quiet stretches,
但我不想成为累赘
but I don't want to be a burden.
而且我越来越习惯独处了
Plus, I'm getting used to being on my own.
或者我们可以一起被隔离
Or we could be quarantined together, you know,
顺便把案子办了
work the case.
好啊 这听上去有点意思
Yes, that actually sounds kind of fun.
只是"有点"意思吗
Kind of?
这将是爽翻天的一周
It's gonna be the best week ever.
不好意思 你们没听到我之前提到的
I'm sorry, did you not hear me say
"睾丸部位的极度不适"吗
extreme testicular discomfort?
我们听到了 "坏消息"医生
Yes, we heard you, Dr. Bad News Doctor.
我和Holt警监刚通了话
Okay, so I talked to Captain Holt.
他和Jake都得了腮腺炎
He and Jake have the mumps.
在Holt康复之前我全权负责
I'm in charge until Holt gets better.
好事啊 你想知道自己是否能成为一个优秀的警监
Hello, you wanted to see if you can make a great captain.
这就是你发光发亮的机会
Now's your chance to shine.
你就是那个漂亮的小替角
You're the pretty little understudy.
而那个老去的主角
And the aging lead?
她刚从楼梯上摔了下去
Well, she just fell down the stairs.
现在你要做的是挥着你的翅膀
Now all's you got to do is beat those wings
飞翔
and fly.
接下来两周
So for the next two weeks,
Holt警监要休病假
Captain Holt will be on medical leave,
警监一职由我代理
which means I am the acting captain.
我们是您忠诚的臣民
And we are your royal subjects.
请继续
Do continue.
我希望大家不仅做好本职工作
I want this precinct to get our normal work done,
也要清理证据室
but also, we're gonna clean out the evidence room,
完善社区服务
step up community service,
同时完成另外22项任务
and complete these 22 additional tasks.
每完成一项打个勾
Every time we check one off the list,
就会听到铃声
you're gonna hear this bell.
它象征着胜利
It's the sound of victory.
你该再加条"修理铃铛"
Hmm, you should add "Fix bell" to that list.
隔离期 第2天
- 早上好 警监  - Peralta
- Morning, Captain. - Peralta.
我想给你介绍个人
I'd like to introduce you to someone.
他叫Simon 我恨死他了
His name is Simon, and I hate him.
你好 Simon
Hello, Simon.
这是Balthazar
This is Balthazar.
他是个往我喉咙里喷火的恶魔
He's an evil demon who spits fire in my throat.
甲状腺肿了吧
Goiters, huh?
随你说啦
Anyway.
我把这些餐厅照片都看了一遍
I've been looking over these photographs of the restaurant,
确定了其他几个已知的犯罪团伙
and I've identified several other known mob types.
怎么了 你发现了什么
What is it? Did you see something?
没 我就是突然好冷打了个颤
No, I just got very cold very fast.
现在全身火烧火燎的
And now my entire body is somehow on fire.
腮腺炎讨厌死了
Oh, these mumps are jerks. Whew.
我还在其他几张照片里注意到有辆货车停在餐厅前面
I also noticed this van is parked out front in several other photographs.
我怎么没注意到
I never noticed that.
这家餐厅肯定被监视了
The restaurant must have been under surveillance.
我估计是政府的人
I bet it was the feds.
你说得对
You're right.
我去联系局里认识的人
I'll reach out to my contact at the bureau,
看看能不能拿到点录像
see if I can get us some footage.
好主意
Good idea.
哦对 虽然知道不可以
Also, I know you're not supposed to,
但是我好想戳戳自己的腮腺炎
but I kind of want to poke my mump.
- 别想了  - 我要戳了
- Bad idea. - I'm going in.
要戳了
Here we go.
痛死了
It hurts!
真没想到会这么疼
How did I not see that coming?
有点儿晕
I feel dizzy.
嘿 你终于爬起来了
Hey. You're off the floor.
是啊
Yeah.
就像我爸以前常说的
Well, it's like my dad used to say.
"是男人就别哭
"Real men don't cry
超过三天"
for more than three days."
所以我决定重振旗鼓回来工作
So I decided to get my butt back to work.
不错 你把目击证词都看过了吗
Good. You go through all the witness statements yet?
什么 没有
What? Oh, no.
"工作"是指制作Jason的纪念视频
By "Work," I meant on Jason's in memoriam video.
- 你认真的吗  - 当然
- Are you serious? - Oh, yeah.
给你看我做好的
Take a look at what I got so far.
Michael Bolton <How Am I Supposed to Live without You>
*告诉我没有你我要怎么活*
*Tell me how am I supposed to live without you*
*我已经爱了你这么久*
*Now that I've been lovin' you so long*
永远想念你
喂 有好多事要做呢
Hey, we've got a lot to do.
集中注意力 别再看搞笑的小狗视频了
Focus up and stop watching funny dog videos.
可能是我烧傻了
This might just be the fever talking,
但是这家意大利餐厅八年前未剪辑的镜头
but this unedited footage of an Italian restaurant
可能是我烧傻了
This might just be the fever talking,
但是这家意大利餐厅八年前未剪辑的镜头
but this unedited footage of an Italian restaurant
可能是我看过的最棒的电影了
from eight years ago might be the best movie I've ever seen.
还有 用叉子多怪啊
Also, how weird are forks?
叉子是很诡异 我一直这么觉得
Forks are very weird. I've always thought so.
没错没错 我们是不是感冒药吃多了
Yeah, yeah. Did we take too much cold medicine?
怎么可能
Not by a long shot.
Balthazar可是个饥渴的小贱人
Balthazar is a thirsty bitch.
为你这句喝一杯
Ah, I'll drink to that.
等等 看啊
Wait, look.
是Garkabargo
Garkabargo!
抱歉 没 没法儿说话
Sorry, can't--can't talk.
要次药
Need more medi-jen.
是Garibaldi
Garibaldi!
他在吃蛇啊
He's eating snakes!
不对 是意面
No, it's spaghetti.
永远都在吃意面
It's always spaghetti.
我就说 如果是意面 那也长得太像蛇了
I'm just saying, if that's spaghetti, it looks like snakes.
太棒了 99
That's right, Nine-Nine.
胜利的铃声欣然响起
That's the sound of the victory bell.
我们完成了清单里的一个任务
We just crossed our first task off the list.
我的天 Terry 太棒了
Oh, my goodness. Terry, that is so great.
是哪一项
Which one was it?
- 修理铃铛  - 好的吧
- Fix bell. - All right.
有点小失望 但总算完成一项了
Little less than I had hoped for, but still a thing.
接下来你会一直听到这铃声的
You gonna hear that sound nonstop.
- 放开她 你这野兽  - 给我
- Unhand her, you beast! - Give it to me!
你们他妈在干嘛
What the hell is going on in here?
Hitchcock想偷我的三明治
Hitchcock's trying to steal my sandwich.
才怪 我俩都点了肉球三明治
Well, we both ordered meatball subs,
但是只送来了一个
but they only delivered one.
是我的
It's mine!
同志们 听着 走去三明治店
Guys, guys, look, just walk to the sub shop--
一条街的事儿 再买个三明治
it's a block away-- and get a second sandwich.
- 走去  - 疯了吗你
- Walk? - Are you insane?
那好吧 切两半总行了吧
Fine, cut the damn sandwich in half.
然后呢 机灵鬼 我们一人吃6英寸三明治
And then what, genius? We each eat a 6-inch sub?
和两个半肉球
Two and a half meatballs a piece?
- 你当我们小孩儿吗  - 你以为自己在俄罗斯吗
- Are we children? - What is this, Russia?
够了 都不许吃
Okay, that's it. No one eats the sub.
回去工作
Get back to work!
隔离期 第5天
等下
Wait a minute.
为什么他去了厨房
Why'd he just go in the kitchen?
我们在厨房也有眼线吗
Do we have eyes in the kitchen?
到处都有眼线
There are eyes everywhere, man.
卧 槽 疼 死 了
Ow, ow, achy, achy, ow.
看 他偷偷塞给大厨一张纸条
Look, he slipped the chef a piece of paper.
我猜上面就是他的藏匿地点了
I bet it's the address of his hideout.
大厨知道他藏在哪儿
The chef knows where the hideout is.
大厨叫Richie Lignardi
His name is Richie Lignardi.
找到他 就能找到Garibaldi
We talk to him, we find Garibaldi.
我们现在就出发
We have to go right now.
出什么发
Go where?
天 你脸上是什么
Ah! What's on your face?
哦对 恶心的畸形肿块
Oh, right, uh, yes, my disgusting deformity.
那我这样
Here, let me just--
嘿 你好吗 大妹子
Hey, what's up, girl?
有没有好一点
Better?
没差啦
It's not worse.
我们准备去找线人
We're on our way right now to talk to a lead
他知道Garibaldi藏在哪儿
that knows where Garibaldi's hideout is.
你们还在隔离期啊
You're quarantined.
不能像两座腮腺炎喷泉一样
You can't go outside spewing mumps
把腮腺炎喷得到处都是啊
like a couple of mump fountains.
这样是肯定不行的
Not like this, we can't!
停 你们不能走
Stop, you can't leave at all.
阻止得了你就试试呗
Good luck trying to stop us.
你抓不到我们哒
You'll never catch us!
Usain Bolt 奥运会男子100米和200米记录保持者
Amy快得像Usain Bolt
Amy is Usain Bolt.
这就是你们要找的纸条吗
Is this the piece of paper you're looking for?
你找到地址啦
You found the address?
没有 这是烤通心粉的菜谱
No, it's a recipe for baked ziti.
一直贴在你墙上的啊
It was taped to your wall the entire time.
你们太虚弱了 病得不轻
You're delirious, and you're sick,
肯定是破不了案的
and you definitely didn't solve the case.
都给我回去
You need to go back inside.
办不到 腿动不了了
Well, I can't. My legs stopped working.
啊 我的蛋蛋
Ah, my testicles.
腮腺炎扩散到蛋蛋了
The mumps have reached my testicles.
好了 把毫无用处
All right, just finish taking off your totally ineffective
还带着传染源的外套脱了 休息一下
biohazard suits and have a little rest.
胡扯 Santiago
Nonsense, Santiago.
我们得勒紧裤腰 努力工作
We just have to buckle down and work harder.
只是受了点小挫折
We simply hit a bump in the road.
更像受了点腮腺炎
More like a mump in the road.
疼得厉害吧
Such a good one.
Jake 能跟你私聊一下吗
Jake, can I talk to you in private for a minute?
当然 我拿条围巾 把肿块挡挡
Sure thing, let me just snag this, cover up the ol' swell sack.
好
All right.
听着 情况是这样的
Okay, so here's the deal.
我发高烧了 控制不了身体
I have a high fever, and I can't control my body,
你想对我做什么都行
but you can do whatever you want to me.
但是 别碰我的嘴 脖子 和蛋蛋
Oh, but don't touch my mouth, neck, or testicles.
你完全误会我的意思了
You've badly misread the situation.
感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
Jake 放弃这个案子吧
Jake, you need to drop this case.
说什么呢你
What are you talking about?
我们的计划实施得很完美
The plan is working perfectly.
Holt这一周都没闲着
Holt hasn't been lonely all week.
没错 因为他忙得快挂了
Yeah, because he's too busy almost dying.
- 你看他  - 怎么了
- Look at him. - What?
他像<美丽心灵>的主角一样
He's just "Beautiful Mind"-ing it.
因为他是天才啊
Because he's a genius.
他在不停地写"案子"这俩字
He's writing the word "Case" Over and over again.
糟了 他开始写"安子"了
Oh, now he's spelling it with a K.
难道不是这么写的吗
Is that not how you spell it?
都说了 我烧得嘴 脖子和蛋蛋都要融化了
Again, I have a mouth, neck, and testicle-melting fever.
- Jake  - 怎么
- Jake. - Hmm?
到此为止
Enough is enough.
放弃这个蠢逼无聊的旧案子
You need to drop this stupid backburner cold case
否则要么你们死 要么我就杀了你
before you both die or I will kill you.
我天 我还以为自己跟上她的思维了呢
Oh, my God, I thought I was following her.
好吧 我还是躺下吧
Yep, I should probably lie down.
我 躺
Here we go.
案子
Case!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
把Jason的项圈密封在袋子里
Just sealing Jason's collar in an airtight bag
这样就能留住他的气味
so it retains his scent.
不知道我还剩多少味道能闻了
I don't know how many whiffs I have left.
吃惊
Wow.
我知道那条狗对你来说很重要
Look, I know that dog meant a lot to you,
所以我给你带了这个
so I got you this.
一只狗
It's a dog.
他叫Arlo 但是你也可以叫他Jason二号
His name's Arlo, but you can call him Jason Two
或者其他名字
or whatever.
认真的
Seriously?
我不能就这么随便地用另一只狗来代替Jason
I can't just replace Jason with some other dog.
为什么 基本上所有狗都一样
Why not? All dogs are basically the same.
看好了 Arlo 快去干那个玩具
Watch this. Arlo, go hump that toy.
别碰它
Get away from that.
那是Jason的
That's Jason's.
听着 伙计 我已经很耐心了
Look, man, I've been patient.
我们有个案子要查
We have a case we need to work on.
是时候忘了这件事朝前看了
It's time for you to get over it, move on.
朝前看 朝前看
Move on? Move on.
Jason是我家的一份子 Rosa
Jason was part of my family, Rosa.
我爱他
I loved him.
他发情是唯一能让我撑过离婚的动力
His humping was the only thing that got me through my divorce.
看见他那么开心我就觉得
Seeing him so happy made me believe
也许有一天我也能那么开心
that I could be happy one day too.
你不会明白这种感受的
You wouldn't understand this
因为你有摩托车头盔来抵御真心
because you have a motorcycle helmet for a heart,
但我需要感受这份悲伤
but I need to feel this sadness.
所以我现在唯一要离开向前看的就是你
So the only thing that I'm moving on from is you.
所以 我好像 有了一只狗
So I, like, have a dog now?
嘿 那些文件看得怎么样了
Hey, what's going on with those files?
我们没在研究那些
Oh, we're not working on them.
- 我们在罢工  - 绝食抗议
- We're on strike. - Hunger strike.
- 可你在吃薯片  - 薯片不算数
- You're eating potato chips. - Chips don't count.
我的医生说薯片一点营养价值都没有
My doctor said they have zero nutritional value.
我们要肉丸三明治
We want meatball subs.
你没有权利拿走我们的食物
You had no right to take ours.
气死我吧
Screw this.
我会整理好这些文件 教危险品的课程
I'll log those files and teach the hazmat class,
我会把所有人的活儿都干了 因为很明显
and I'll do everyone's work, because apparently,
我是唯一一个能让这个分局凝聚在一起的人
I am the only one keeping this precinct together!
呃 我觉得你关门太用力了
Um, I think you closed the door too hard.
我找到了雪糕
Hey, I found popsicles.
这应该能帮我们降温
These should help cool us down.
谢啦 Jake
"Thanks, Jake."
不客气 蛋蛋君
You're welcome, nards.
Peralta Balthzar有个姐妹
Peralta, Balthazar has a sister.
叫做Penelope
Meet Penelope.
哈哈 你两边都肿了
Guh-hoo, yeah, mumps on mumps.
不要在意细节 我们赶紧开始工作
Let's not dwell on it. We should get back to work.
或者我们也可以睡个五到七天
Or we could fall asleep for five to seven days
然后看看感觉如何
and see how we feel.
正义得到伸张之前我不会休息的
I will not rest till justice is served.
别浪费时间了
There's no time to waste.
这个案子非常紧急
This case is urgent.
天
Oh, boy.
好吧 听好了
All right, listen.
这个案子其实没我们开始想的那么紧急
The case may not be quite as urgent as once thought.
嗯
Um...
这是我从桌上挖出来
I dug it up out of my desk so you'd have something
让你在周末有些事做的 因为你看起来非常孤单
to do on weekends because you seemed so lonely.
你听说Garibaldi卷土重来了
You cited chatter from the streets that Garibaldi had resurfaced.
确实 没错 就是这样
I did. I did. I did.
但那些可能只是胡说八道
But said chatter may have been fudged.
所以你骗了我
So you lied to me?
出于同情 你同情我
Out of pity. You pity me.
话不是这么说的
I wouldn't put it that way.
我就是这么觉得的
I would.
我受到了冒犯 我很生气
I am offended. I am angry.
我觉得很累
I am very tired.
所以我要睡一觉 但当我醒来
So I'm gonna take a nap, but when I wake up,
你要为此付出代价
oh, you are in for it.
4小时后
你怎么敢
How dare you?
我怎么敢
How dare me?
你怎么敢
How dare you?
我只是想要帮忙
I was just trying to help.
你的帮助感觉太像同情了
Wow, your help feels an awful lot like pity,
所以帮帮忙 别再帮我了
so do me a favor and don't ever help me again.
哇 你好像不在意我帮你
Wow, well, you didn't seem to mind me helping you
找回你在99分局的工作
when I got you your job back at the Nine-Nine.
我又没要你帮忙
I didn't ask you to do that.
你说我们没有豆子了 你这个偷豆子的猪
You said we were out of peas, you pea hog!
- 你才是偷豆子的猪  - 你才是偷豆子的猪
- You're the pea hog! - You're the pea hog!
- 不 你是  - 你收回那句话
- No, you! - You take that back!
你
You!
双重攻击
Double poke!
希望你们都饿了
Okay, hope you guys are hungry.
我做了烤通心粉
Made baked ziti.
我觉得用Garibaldi的菜谱会很有意思呢
Thought it would be fun to use Garibaldi's ultra authentic recipe.
太棒了 出于同情的食物
Oh, great, pity food.
不管怎样谢谢你 但是我自己可以做饭
Thank you anyway, but I can cook for myself.
如果不是因为那样脑子会疼的话
Wow, I would roll my eyes so hard right now
我早就在翻白眼了
if it didn't make my brain burn.
好了警监 别闹脾气了
Okay, Captain, this ends now.
我知道你的自尊受到了伤害
I know your pride is hurt,
但从来没有人同情你
but no one ever took pity on you.
我们只是想在你不开心的时候帮助你
All we wanted to do was help you when you were down.
因为那就是人们在关心彼此的时候会做的事
Because that's what people do when they care about each other.
他们会向彼此撒谎
They tell each other lies
并无中生有出一些急需解决的案子吗
and invent urgent mysteries that need to be solved?
是找点在一起的理由
Come up with excuses to spend time together
就像问答之夜或者民间艺术节
like trivia nights or folk art festivals.
还有和他们腮腺炎小伙伴Jake一起调查积灰的案子
Or working old-ass cases with their mumpy boy, Jake.
你继续 Amy 我们干得不错
Back to you, Amy. We're doing great.
你把通心粉吃了 你会喜欢它的
You're gonna eat this ziti, and you're gonna appreciate it,
然后你给我赶紧成熟起来
and you're gonna grow the hell up.
好吧 你是对的
Okay, you're right.
我为我的行为感到抱歉
I'm sorry for the way I acted.
我迫不及待要尝尝你的手艺了
I can't wait to eat your food.
这难吃得要吐了
Ugh, this is revolting.
你还是什么都没有学到吗
Wow, have you learned nothing?
天哪
Oh, God!
这比腮腺炎还恐怖 Amy
That is worse than the mumps, Amy.
什么鬼
What the hell?
我完全按照Garibaldi的食谱做的
I used Garibaldi's exact recipe.
我知道我不是个好厨子
I know I'm not a great cook,
但是我超爱听从指示的
but I love following instructions.
七杯盐
Seven cups of salt?
就算是我也知道这不会是张菜谱了
Even I know this isn't a recipe.
也就是说这可能是份密码
Which means it might be a code.
有意思
Ooh, interesting.
十位数 这可能是个电话号码
Ten digits, maybe it's a phone number.
看 718 布鲁克林区号
Look, 718, Brooklyn area code.
没错 一定是这样
Yes, that's definitely it.
等等 你真的加了这么多盐
Wait, did you actually use all of this salt
还有18杯牛至
and 18 cups of oregano?
你别管 我破了案子
Back off, I solved the case.
9个洋葱
Nine onions?
哦 Amy
Oh, Amy.
我怎么就成坏人了
How am I the bad guy here?
99分局
3天后
好吧好吧 这看起来不错
All right, all right, looks good.
我都看不出来这里曾经被绿巨人毁灭过一次了
I can barely tell you hulked out in here.
是啊 但是我主管了两周
Yeah, but two weeks in charge,
却一个目标都没有完成
and I didn't get any of my goals accomplished.
你让Hitchcock和Scully停止绝食抗议了
You got Hitchcock and Scully off their hunger strike.
我只是把一把爆米花扔到了地上
I just threw a bunch of popcorn on the floor.
一点都不难
It wasn't that hard.
是啊 他们就像动物一样
Yeah, they're animals.
你知道为什么神奇的Holt警监
Do you want to know why the amazing Captain Holt
从来没能清理好证据室
has never gotten the evidence room cleaned
或者完成你列表上的任何事吗
or done anything on your list?
为什么
Why?
因为他总在处理同事之间的摩擦
Because all day long, he's putting out fires.
这就是警监的工作
That's what a captain does.
你和Holt的唯一区别就是
The only difference between you and Holt is that
他没有你这样的神力 关个门就能让一间房散架
he lacks the strength to close a door so hard a room blows up.
谢谢 Gina
Thanks, Gina.
你不用感谢我
Ah, you don't have to thank me.
我所做的只是做那个唯一相信你的人
All I did was be the only person who believes in you.
别靠着门
Don't lean against the door.
Terry造成了结构损伤
Terry caused structural damage.
天哪 你太壮了
My God, you're strong.
去简报室 现在
Briefing room, now.
我真的不想再被你教训了
I really don't feel like having you yell at me anymore.
这是什么
What is this?
这是Jason的葬礼
It's a funeral for Jason.
我有些话想说
I want to say a few words.
当七天前Jason去世的时候 我一丁点儿都不在乎
When Jason died seven days ago, I didn't give a rat's ass.
这就是你的发言
This is your speech?
因为我不懂为什么人们这么在乎他们蠢兮兮的狗
'Cause I didn't understand why people care so much about their dumb dogs
直到我自己有了一只狗
till I got a dumb dog myself.
我只养了Arlo一天半
I've only had Arlo for a day and a half,
但如果他出了任何事
but if anything happened to him,
我会杀了这个房间里的所有人然后自杀
I would kill everyone in this room and then myself.
非常暴力的颂词 我喜欢
Very violent eulogy, I like it.
Charles 我很抱歉
Charles, I'm sorry.
你不需要尽快跨过这道坎
You don't have to get over it.
尽情沉浸在悲伤吧
Take as long as you want.
Scully 就现在
Scully, it's time.
好的 谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
好消息 Garibaldi的手机号还在使用
Good news, Garibaldi's phone number's still active,
所以他们能够找出他的位置
so they were able to locate him.
特警刚刚抓住了他 就是这样
SWAT just picked him up, so that's that.
是啊 就是这样
Yeah, that's that.
完美的时间 我们的隔离期终于结束了
Perfect timing as our quarantine has finally ended
甲状腺肿块也终于消了
and our goiters are gone.
是啊 没错
Yes, indeed.
我们可以出门去 想舔谁的眼珠就舔谁的眼珠
We're free to go outside and lick whoever's eyeballs we'd like.
不太对 没人有这个权力
Inaccurate, no one is ever free to do that.
好吧 你是对的
Yeah, you're right.
不管怎样 我出去了
Anyhow, I am out.
等一等
Wait a minute.
我很抱歉之前冲你吼叫
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
我太骄傲了 所以我不想承认我很孤单
I was too proud to admit I was lonely.
所以谢谢你
So thank you.
不用客气
You're welcome.
不算事儿
Ain't no thang.
不 这算事儿 更算事儿的是你
No, it is a thang, and an even bigger thang
让我回到了99分局
is that you brought me back to the Nine-Nine,
我会永远感激这件事的
and I will always be grateful for that.
所以这个
So, here.
这是给你的
This is for you.
酸糖果 我想死你们了
Sour candies. I missed you so much.
疼死我了
This burns.
多谢你的礼物
Thank you for this gift.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组